{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Cabinet Refinishing Contractors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40179/":{"taskOID":40179,"originalTaskOID":40179,"setID":488,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4372,"questionDisplayText":"Select refinish location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select the location where the cabinets will be refinished.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2730,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage/work area","answerDisplayText":"Garage/work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4374,"questionDisplayText":"Refinishing type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of refinishing do you want done to your cabinets? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Change color of paint","answerDisplayText":"Change color of paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color of stain","answerDisplayText":"Change color of stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6149,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strip paint and stain","answerDisplayText":"Strip paint and stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3590,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighten as much as possible","answerDisplayText":"Lighten as much as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1963,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Distressed look","answerDisplayText":"Distressed look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3722,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Make new and old cabinets match","answerDisplayText":"Make new and old cabinets match","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":823,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Apply special finish","answerDisplayText":"Apply special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5327,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Restore existing color","answerDisplayText":"Restore existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4297,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Not sure, need advice","answerDisplayText":"Not sure, need advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4370,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinet Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the existing cabinets made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4372,"questionDisplayText":"Select refinish location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select the location where the cabinets will be refinished.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2730,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage/work area","answerDisplayText":"Garage/work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":986,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Bathroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2380,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Family room","answerDisplayText":"Family room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1005,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Bedroom(s)","answerDisplayText":"Bedroom(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2730,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Garage/work area","answerDisplayText":"Garage/work area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3628,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Living room","answerDisplayText":"Living room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1926,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Dining room","answerDisplayText":"Dining room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2909,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Hallway","answerDisplayText":"Hallway","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3478,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Laundry room","answerDisplayText":"Laundry room","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4374,"questionDisplayText":"Refinishing type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of refinishing do you want done to your cabinets? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Change color of paint","answerDisplayText":"Change color of paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color of stain","answerDisplayText":"Change color of stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6149,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strip paint and stain","answerDisplayText":"Strip paint and stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3590,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighten as much as possible","answerDisplayText":"Lighten as much as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1963,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Distressed look","answerDisplayText":"Distressed look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3722,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Make new and old cabinets match","answerDisplayText":"Make new and old cabinets match","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":823,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Apply special finish","answerDisplayText":"Apply special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5327,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Restore existing color","answerDisplayText":"Restore existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4297,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Not sure, need advice","answerDisplayText":"Not sure, need advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4542,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Paint","answerDisplayText":"Paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1334,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Change color of paint","answerDisplayText":"Change color of paint","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1335,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color of stain","answerDisplayText":"Change color of stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6149,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Strip paint and stain","answerDisplayText":"Strip paint and stain","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3590,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Lighten as much as possible","answerDisplayText":"Lighten as much as possible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1963,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Distressed look","answerDisplayText":"Distressed look","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3722,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Make new and old cabinets match","answerDisplayText":"Make new and old cabinets match","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":823,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Apply special finish","answerDisplayText":"Apply special finish","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5327,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Restore existing color","answerDisplayText":"Restore existing color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4297,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Not sure, need advice","answerDisplayText":"Not sure, need advice","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4370,"questionDisplayText":"Cabinet Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Of what material are the existing cabinets made?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4561,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Painted wood","answerDisplayText":"Painted wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6015,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stained wood","answerDisplayText":"Stained wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3441,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Laminate","answerDisplayText":"Laminate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40179/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40179,"taskName":"Cabinets - Refinish","taskDescription":"Refinish Already Installed Cabinets","xmTaskDescriptor":"Cabinet Refinishing Contractors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":31,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Cabinets Refinsh countertops custom,cabinetry","textMessagingName":"Refinish Cabinets","rolloverLongDesc":"Appropriate when a renewed natural or stained appearance is desired. For cabinet painting, see interior painting.","rolloverShortDesc":"Strip \u0026 refinish existing wood cabinets.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Refinish Already Installed Cabinets.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Cabinet Refinishing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Cabinet Refinishing","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":8,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Cabinets - Refinish","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Cabinets - Refinish","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Cabinet Refinish Project","urlName":"Cabinets-Refinish","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Cabinet Refinishing Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Kitchen Cabinet Refinishing","searchKeywords":"refinish","emcCategoryOid":-12009,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":488,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}